Finding Aid for Lincoln Highway Association Records, 1911-1941
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- Miscellaneous
  - University of Michigan Correspondence
    - May 20, 1943-December 1, 1945 (Box 4)
    - December 3, 1945-October 3, 1946 (Box 4)
    - October 5, 1946-January 9, 1947 (Box 4)
    - February 14, 1947-February 8, 1973 (Box 4)
    - Walt Disney Productions
      - October 9, 1957-October 30, 1957 (Box 4)
      - October 30, 1957-December 13, 1957 (Box 4)
      - December 20, 1957-May 6, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Scrapbooks of clippings and mock-ups of publicity brochures (5 items) (Box 6)
- Jens Jensen Drawings
  The Jens Jensen Drawings series (1922-1924) includes seven sketches by the landscape architect for a Campsite and Filling Station located in the Ideal Section, Lake County, Indiana, which was never built. The drawings are in color pencil on onion paper. Six of the sketches portray the general plan of the campsite from an aerial view. One sketch includes the designs for grease and wash racks, filling station and museum, stove and incinerator, and the camp fire.
  - "A Preliminary Sketch for the Camp Site-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. June 1923" (26in x 36.5in; color) (Port Port. 1)
  - "A Preliminary Sketch for the Camp Grounds-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. December 1922" (26in x 36.5in; color) (Port Port. 1)
  - "A Preliminary Sketch for the Camp Site-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. July 1923" (21.5in x 38.5in; b&w) (Port Port. 1)
  - "A Preliminary Sketch for the Camp Site-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. December 1923" (16.5in x 37in; color) (Port Port. 1)
  - "Campsite with Estimates, [July ] 1924" (16in x 39.5in; color) (Port Port. 1)
  - "Details for Camp Site-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. May 1924" (11.75in x 38.5in; color) (Port Port. 1)
  - "A Preliminary Sketch for the Camp Site-Ideal Section-Lincoln Highway. Lake County-Indiana. May 1924" (drawing: 25in x 35in; framed: 28.25in x 41.25in; color) (CANTILEVER WEST) (Port Port. 1)